

@ acye2002@gmail.com

90229881

Singapore

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Driven student leveraging studies in Immersive Media seeks real-world experience as UI/UX Designer, Web Designer. Offers strong interpersonal and task prioritization skills.

Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals.

### **WORK HISTORY**

March 2021 - Current Empire Code - Freelance Trainer , Singapore

October 2018 - November 2018 HARD ROCK HOTEL -WAITER, Singapore

- Preparation of morning and lunch buffet
- Maintain clean look for tables and buffet counter
- Serve customers needs when needed

## CHIN YUNG ERN (AARON)

#### **EDUCATION**

Diploma: Immersive Media Ngee Ann Polytechnic, Singapore

- · Member of ICT Society
- · Member of SIG: Overflow, and Nullsec

Nitec in Information Technology Institute of Technical Education, Singapore, November 2020

Graduated with a 4.0 GPA

- Elected to be President for ITE College Central Student Council (From November 2019- November 2020)
- · Director List for Academic Year 19/20
- Received Lee Kuan Yew Scholarship To Encourage Progression (LKY-STEP)
- · Received Chip Eng Seng Study Grant
- · Awarded Lee Kuan Yew Model Student/Trainee Award
- Awarded ITE Outstanding Graduate Award (School of Electronics and Info-Comm Technology)
- Awarded ITE Top Graduate Award (School of Electronics and Info-Comm Technology)
- Awarded Harvard Prize Book (Singapore) 2020/21
- · Awarded Yio Chu Kang Youth Community Leadership Award

Normal Technical Level **Mayflower Secondary School**, Singapore, November 2018

- · Awarded Outstanding Academic Award (2018)
- · Member of Table Tennis Club
- · Awarded Mayflowerian of the Year 2018
- · Awarded Heart of Gold Character Award (2017)
- Awarded Academic Award Best in Mathematics, Secondary Three Normal (Technical) 2017

#### SKILLS

- Team leadership skills
- Project Management
- · Microsoft Power Apps
- · Event Planning
- Issue Resolution
- · Work Planning and Prioritization
- · Verbal and Written Communication
- · Driven and Determined
- · Public Speaking
- Team Collaboration and Leadership
- · Attention to Detail
- · Design principles

#### LINKEDIN, GITHUB, REPLIT

- · https://www.linkedin.com/in/aaroncye/
- · https://github.com/Aaroncye
- https://replit.com/@Aaroncye